storyfluence.com 2017-06-27

# Privacy Policy

_(The below Privacy policy is released under the Creative Commons licenses by[Automattic](https://automattic.com/) — you can use this policy but, be nice, and include a link to their site.)_

Please read the following statements carefully, as they address the rules of engagement between us.

This Website is owned and operated by Tribe Marketing Limited. The following terms and conditions govern your use of this site and all other Tribe Marketing Limited Sites and products listed herein.

For the purpose of this agreement and for ease of use, a reference to “the Company” shall be a reference to Tribe Marketing Limited and a reference to “the Website” shall be a reference to all websites owned by the Company, their respective products, and their employees and agents. The Websites include, but are not limited to: [http://tinylittlebusinesses.com](http://tinylittlebusinesses.com/), [http://andrechaperon.com](http://andrechaperon.com/), [http://anitachaperon.com](http://anitachaperon.com/), [http://frankvsmatt.com](http://frankvsmatt.com/).

By accessing this Website and any of the Company’s properties, you are acknowledging and accepting the conditions of this Privacy Policy for all of the Company’s properties.

These terms of use are subject to change at any time at the discretion of the Company without notice. Your use of any of the Company’s Websites after any changes are implemented constitutes your acceptance of the changes. As a result, we encourage you to consult the terms and conditions herein frequently.

Your privacy is critically important to us. At the Company, we have a few fundamental principles:

  * We do not actively collect sensitive information about you, including information about your health, racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious beliefs, sexual orientation or criminal history. We will take steps to appropriately protect any sensitive information we do receive.
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.
  * In our blogging products, we aim to make it as simple as possible for you to control what’s visible to the public, seen by search engines, kept private, and permanently deleted.

It is the Company’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our Websites.

**WEBSITE VISITORS**

Like most website operators, the Company collects (via its Websites) non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. The Company’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how the Company’s visitors use its Websites. From time to time, the Company may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its Website.

The Company also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. The Company does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described above.  
**  
GATHERING OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION**

Certain visitors to the Company’s Websites choose to interact with us in ways that require us to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that the Company gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. The Company collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with the Company. The Company does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

**PROTECTION OF CERTAIN PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION**

The Company discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on the Company’s behalf or to provide services available at the Company’s Websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using the Company’s Websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. The Company will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, the Company discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when the Company believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of the Company, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of any of the Company’s Websites and have supplied your email address, the Company may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with the Company and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. The Company takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

**AGGREGATED STATISTICS**

The Company may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. The Company may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, the Company does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

**COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES**

Cookies are small text files of information stored by your internet browser on your computer’s hard drive. We may use cookies to collect browsing data, for example, to keep track of your preferences and profile information and to collect general usage and volume statistical information. Our cookies do not collect personal, confidential information and are not spyware.

You may set your internet web browser to refuse cookies or to remove cookies from your hard drive.

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. The Company uses cookies to help the Company identify and track visitors, their usage of The Company’s Websites, and their Websites access preferences. The Company’s visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using the Company’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of the Company’s Websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

**ADS**

If any ads appear on any of our Websites, they may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by the Company and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**SURVEYS & CONSENTS**

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

**YOUR CONSENT**

By using any of the Company’s Websites you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

**CHOICE/OPT-OUT**

You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails at any time, by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails, by updating your communications preferences via our email service provider, or you can contact us via our Support page.

**TESTIMONIALS**

If you provide us with a testimonial, you give us your consent for the use of your name and the Service to be displayed on any of the Company’s Websites, or in our other marketing materials, together with the content of the testimonial that you provide.

**COMMENTS**

Comments and other content submitted to our Akismet anti-spam service are not saved on our servers unless they were marked as false positives, in which case we store them long enough to use them to improve the service to avoid future false positives.

**TERMINATION**

We may cancel or terminate your right to use some or any of the Company’s sites or any part of those sites at any time without notice, and at our discretion. In the event of cancellation or termination, you are no longer authorized to access the part or parts of the sites affected by such cancellation or termination. The restrictions imposed on you with respect to material downloaded from any of the Company’s sites, and the disclaimers and limitations of liabilities set forth in these Terms of Service, shall survive.

**CHILDREN’S PRIVACY**

The Website is not intended for use by children under the age of 13. We will not knowingly collect personal information from them. If we discover that a child has provided us with personal information, we will use reasonable efforts to delete this information. If you have reason to believe we may have accidentally received personal information from a child under the age of 13, please immediately submit details through our Support page.

**ABOUT THE PRIVACY POLICY**

The entire contents of this Privacy Policy should be read in conjunction with our Terms of Services & Disclaimer.

If you do not understand any of the contents in this Privacy Policy, or if you have any questions or comments, we invite you to contact us via our Support page.

_This Privacy Policy was last updated February 2017._
